Guide to the Edwin H. Armstrong papers,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series IV: Alphabetical Files, 1886-1980
  - RCA Litigation
    - Armstrong v. RCA and NBC
      - Crosby, Murray G.
        - Notes and Abstract of Crosby Notebooks, 1952 (Box 110, Folder 1)
        - Crosby Exhibits--Notes and Research, 1931-1952 (Box 110, Folder 2)
          - 46-78, 1930-1939, (2 Folders) (Box 110, Folder 3-4)
          - 27-105, 1930-1952, (4 Folders) (Box 110, Folder 5-8)
        - Crosby Notebooks
          - No. 1 and 1A--Photostats, 1931 (Box 110, Folder 9)
          - No. 1B, 1930 (Box 110, Folder 10)
          - No. 5, 1929 (Box 110, Folder 11)
          - No. 6, 1930-1931 (Box 110, Folder 12)
          - No. 7, 1931 (Box 110, Folder 13)
          - No. 8, 1932 (Box 110, Folder 14)
          - No. 9, 1933-1934 (Box 110, Folder 15)
          - No. 10, 1934-1935 (Box 110, Folder 16)
          - No. 11, 1935-1936 (Box 110, Folder 17)
          - No. 12-13, 1937-1942 (Box 110, Folder 18)
        - Notes on Crosby Notebooks, 1952 (Box 110, Folder 19)
        - Crosby Patent 2,230,212--File History, 1940-1955 (Box 110, Folder 20)
        - Crosby Application 2,114,335, 1933-1935 (Box 110, Folder 21)
          - 2,230,231, 1937-1941 (Box 110, Folder 22)
          - 2,081,577, 1932-1937 (Box 110, Folder 23)
        - Crosby Patents, 1927-1952, (3 Folders) (Box 111, Folder 1-3)
          - Patent 2,229,640, 1941 (Box 111, Folder 4)
        - Record and Brief, undated (Box 111, Folder 5)
        - Crosby, M.G.--"Binaural Sound on One FM Channel," 1953 (Box 111, Folder 6)
          - "Communication by Phase Modulation," 1939 (Box 111, Folder 7)
          - "Exalted-Carrier Amplitude and Phase Modulation Reception," 1945 (Box 111, Folder 8)
          - "Frequency Modulation Propagation Characteristics," 1936 (Box 111, Folder 9)
          - Preliminary Write-up of "Service Range of FM," 1939, (2 Folders) (Box 111, Folder 10-11)
          - "FM Noise Characteristics," 1937 (Box 111, Folder 12)
      - General, 1941-1954 (Box 111, Folder 13)
      - REL-DAY "Serrasoid" Matter--D.M. Raymond, 1951 (Box 111, Folder 14)
      - Complaint, 1948 (Box 111, Folder 15)
      - Memorandum Regarding Pre-Trial Examinations of Defendant's by Plaintiff, 1949 (Box 111, Folder 16)
      - Armstrong v. FCC--Memoranda, 1949 (Box 111, Folder 17)
      - Correspondence and Legal Memoranda, 1952 (Box 111, Folder 18)
      - Horizons Titanium Corporation--Correspondence, 1952-1954 (Box 111, Folder 19)
      - Dunn, Gano--Correspondence, 1933-1939 (Box 111, Folder 20)
      - General, 1930-1944 (Box 111, Folder 21)
      - Requests for Production of Documents by Defendants, 1951-1952, (2 Folders) (Box 111, Folder 22-23)
      - Documents Regarding Allocation of F-2-8 Rewrite, 1935 (Box 111, Folder 24)
      - Circuit Diagrams by Pilot Radio Corp., 1946-1952 (Box 111, Folder 25)
      - Documents Examined April 2, 1950--Correspondence and Articles, 1935-1941 (Box 112, Folder 1)
      - Documents Examined April 1, 1950--Correspondence, 1939-1943 (Box 112, Folder 2)
      - Documents Selected as of April 2, 1950--FM Notes and Bibliography, undated (Box 112, Folder 3)
      - General, 1931-1954 (Box 112, Folder 4)
      - Diagrams, 1953 (Box 112, Folder 5)
      - Receiver Diagram and Data, 1953 (Box 112, Folder 6)
      - Supplement to Schedule of FM Apparatus and Descriptive Material, 1949 (Box 112, Folder 7)
      - Bell Telephone--General, 1935-1953 (Box 112, Folder 8)
      - Supplemental Request for Submission under Rule 36A, 1953 (Box 112, Folder 9)
      - Radio Receivers--Advertisements, Catalogs and Diagrams, 1945-1949, (2 Folders) (Box 112, Folder 10-11)
      - Schematic Diagram, 1948 (Box 112, Folder 12)
      - Broadcast Receiver Notes, undated (Box 112, Folder 13)
      - Artificial Line, 1952 (Box 112, Folder 14)
      - Television Receiver Ads, 1949 (Box 112, Folder 15)
      - Correspondence with Mobile and Miscellaneous Communication Licensees, 1949-1955 (Box 112, Folder 16)
      - Harry Sadenwater's Notes, 1949 (Box 112, Folder 17)
      - Broadcast Receiving Set License Agreements--A through Z, 1939-1949, (4 Folders) (Box 112, Folder 18-21)
      - Correspondence with Broadcast Receiving Set Licensees--D.M. Raymond, 1948-1956 (Box 112, Folder 22)
      - Hansell, Clarence
        - US Patent Office--Transcript of Record, undated (Box 112, Folder 23)
        - Brief for Edwin Armstrong--Petition for Rehearing--Memorandum for Hansell, 1947 (Box 112, Folder 24)
        - Various Characteristics Run by Lab with Respect to Hansell Predistortion via John H. Bose, 1949-1951 (Box 112, Folder 25)
        - Abstracts of Hansell Testimony, 1950 (Box 112, Folder 26)
        - Calculations Regarding Hansell's Pre-emphasis Patent, undated (Box 112, Folder 27)
        - Hansell Interference--Transcripts and Briefs, 1947 (Box 113, Folder 1)
        - Patent Application 1,938,657, 1929-1933 (Box 113, Folder 2)
        - Patent Application 1,999,902, 1932-1935 (Box 113, Folder 3)
        - Patent Application 2,088,203, 1933-1937 (Box 113, Folder 4)
        - Documents to be Introduced as Exhibits--Calculations and Drawings, undated (Box 113, Folder 5)
        - Hansell Exhibits sent to D.M. Raymond on November 19, 1957 (Box 113, Folder 6)
        - Exhibits--Duplicates, undated (Box 113, Folder 7)
        - Notes on Hansell Testimony, 1952, undated (Box 113, Folder 8)
        - Exhibits in Hansell Interference--Includes Drawings, Photographs and Correspondence, 1935-1941, undated (Box 113, Folder 9)
        - Hansell Predistortion Calculations--Also Predistortion Calculations of Some Hathaway Work, 1951, undated (Box 113, Folder 10)
        - Examination Notes, 1952 (Box 113, Folder 11)
        - References for German Opposition, 1952-1953 (Box 113, Folder 12)
        - Examination Notes, 1952 (Box 113, Folder 13)
        - Hansell Interference--RCA Research Division Technical Report, 1933 (Box 113, Folder 14)
        - US Patent Office--Briefs and Transcripts, undated, (2 Folders) (Box 113, Folder 15-16)
      - Legal Documents--Memoranda for Files--D.M. Raymond, McCormack, and Byerly,1940-1952, (4 Folders) (Box 113, Folder 17-20)
      - Legal Documents--Motions Before the District Court for District of Delaware, 1948-1951, undated, (6 Folders) (Box 114, Folder 1-6)
      - Chart--Validity Issues--Issues, Patents and Types of Evidence, undated (Box 259, Folder 1)
      - Numbered Documents--For Use in Litigation--Photographs
        - 1 through 1,743, (14 Folders) (Box 150, Folder 1-14)
        - 1,744 through 3,286, (14 Folders) (Box 151, Folder 1-14)
        - 3,287 through 4,186, (15 Folders) (Box 152, Folder 1-15)
        - 4,187 through 5,455, (16 Folders) (Box 153, Folder 1-16)
        - 5,456 through 6,262, (15 Folders) (Box 154, Folder 1-15)
        - 6,263 through 7,496, (16 Folders) (Box 155, Folder 1-16)
        - 7,497 through 8,633, (15 Folders) (Box 156, Folder 1-15)
        - 8,634 through 11,475, (17 Folders) (Box 157, Folder 1-17)
        - 11,476 through 12,725, (18 Folders) (Box 158, Folder 1-18)
        - 12,726 through 13,723, (19 Folders) (Box 159, Folder 1-19)
        - 13, 724 through 14,988, (20 Folders) (Box 160, Folder 1-20)
        - 14,989 through 15,872, (19 Folders) (Box 161, Folder 1-19)
        - 15,873 through 16,794, (20 Folders) (Box 162, Folder 1-20)
        - 16,795 through 17,547, (15 Folders) (Box 163, Folder 1-15)
        - 17,548 through 18,628, 30,001 through 30,512, (15 Folders) (Box 164, Folder 1-15)
        - 30,513 through 30,730, 40,000 through 40,039, 50,128 through 50,255, (6 Folders) (Box 165, Folder 1-6)
      - Transcripts--Volumes
        - Edwin H. Armstrong v. Radio Corporation of America and National Broadcasting Company, Civil Action # 1139 In the District Court of the United States for the District of Delaware
          - Deposition of Edwin H. Armstrong
            - 1949 February 14-15; March 2-4, 10, 14, 17, 24; April 4-5, 12, 15, 20-21, 25-26; May 19, 24, 26-27; June 2, 27, 29; July 8 (Box 166)
            - 1949 November 10, 14-15, 17-18, 21-22, 23, 28, 30; December 2, 12-14, 16, 19; 1950 January 23; February 3,6, 10, 20 (Box 167)
          - Depositions
            - Joe W Morrison and Allen Barco, 1950 February 20 (Box 168)
            - Edward W. Wilby, Jack Avins and Carl W. Zemke, 1950 February 23 (Box 168)
            - Kenneth A. Chittick, 1950 June 13-14, 27, September 27 (Box 168)
            - Chester M. Sinnett and Arthur Floyd Van Dyck, 1950 June 27 (Box 168)
            - Stuart W. Seeley, 1950 September 29 (Box 168)
          - Examinations
            - Raymond Guy and O. B. Hanson, 1950 October 11 (Box 168)
            - Dominic Schmit and Clarence W. Hansell, 1950 October 19-20 (Box 168)
            - Harold O. Peterson, 1950 November 1, 3 (Box 168)
          - Depositions
            - Gano Dunn, 1950 November 3 (Box 168)
            - Harold O. Peterson, Raymond Guy and O. B. Hanson, 1950 November 30 (Box 168)
            - O. B. Hanson, 1950 December 12, 14-15, 18-19
              - 1951 January 4, 10, 15 (Box 169)
            - Elmer W. Engstrom, 1951 January 17-18, 23-24 (Box 169)
            - George M. Nixon, 1951 January 25 (Box 169)
            - Clarence W. Hansell, 1951 January 31, February 1, 27-28, March 1 (Box 169)
            - Nils E. Lindenblad, 1951 March 12 (Box 169)
            - Murray G. Crosby, 1951 April 6, 10, 12 (Box 169)
            - Ralph W. George, 1951 April 11 (Box 169)
            - Ralph W. George and Deposition of Orville Dow, 1951 April 16 (Box 169)
            - Walter Spiegel and Marcus Glaser, 1951 April 27 (Box 170)
            - Marcus Glaser, 1951 April 30 (Box 170)
            - Murray G. Crosby, 1951 May 3,10, 15, 17, June 8, September 20, October 10, 17, 30, November 7, 15, 29 (Box 170)
            - David. G. C. Luck, 1951 May 9 (Box 170)
            - Leo J. Galanek, 1951 May 9 (Box 170)
            - Harry Tunick, 1951 October 4, 9, 16, 22, 31, November 5, 13, 20, 26 (Box 170)
            - Murray G. Crosby, 1951 December 6, 13, 1952 January 16 (Box 171)
            - Clarence W.Hansell, 1951 December 7 (Box 171)
            - Harry Tunick, 1951 December 11, 27, 1952 January 3, February 1, 15 (Box 171)
            - Gano Dunn, 1951 December 20, 1952 January 9 (Box 171)
            - Harold Henry Beverage, 1952 January 8, 15, 24, 31 (Box 171)
            - Robert E. Shelby, Thomas J. Buzalski and William A. R. Brown, 1952 January 23 (Box 171)
            - Charles B. Jolliffe, 1952 February 6 (Box 171)
            - Jarrett L. Hathaway, 1952 February 13, March 4, 13 (Box 171)
            - Wendell L. Carlson, 1952 February 14, March 6 (Box 171)
            - Vernon D. Landon, 1952 March 13 (Box 171)
            - Harry Tunick, 1952 March 14, 18, April 25, May 9, 23, 27, June 11, 30 (Box 172)
            - William H. Conron, R. L. Harvey and R.S. Holmes, 1952 March 19 (Box 172)
            - Charles B. Jolliffe, 1952 April 2, 17, May 8, June 4 (Box 172)
            - Robert M. Morris,1952 April 3 (Box 172)
            - Clarence W. Hansell,1952 April 4, 11, May 23 (Box 172)
            - Benjamin Abrams, Dorman D. Israel and Raymond Herzog, 1952 April 15 (Box 172)
            - Dorman D. Israel and Raymond Herzog, 1952 April 16 (Box 172)
            - Paul de Mars, 1952 May 13, June 25 (Box 172)
            - Irving Wolff,1952 May 29 (Box 172)
            - Ewen C. Anderson,1952 June 19 (Box 172)
            - Joseph D. Black,1952 June 25 (Box 172)
            - Harold O. Peterson,1952 August 12 (Box 173)
            - Harry Tunick, 1952 August 12, 15, 20, 27, September 3, 17 (Box 173)
            - Benjamin E. Shackelfold, 1952 August 15, 18 (Box 173)
            - Elmer E. Lucher,1952 August 29 (Box 173)
            - Robert E. Schock and George W. Pettengill,1952 September 4 (Box 173)
            - Murray G. Crosby,1952 September 12, October 8, 15 (Handwritten Annotations Page Inserted), 22 (Box 173)
            - Ernest V. Amy,1952 September 1 (Box 173)
          - Oral Arguments,1952 September 19, October 10, 23 (Box 173)
          - Depositions
            - Clarence W. Hansell,1952 October 3 (Box 173)
            - Edwin H. Armstrong,1952 October 15, 22 (Box 173)
            - Harry G. Grover,1952 October 16, 24 (Box 173)
            - Stuart W. Seeley,1952 October 28 (Box 173)
            - Orrin E. Dunlap Jr., Phil L. Rodier and James G. Norton,1952 November 3 (Box 173)
            - Harry Tunick,1952 November 7, 14, 19 (Box 174)
          - Oral Argument,1952 November 20 (Box 174)
          - Depositions
            - Otto S. Schairer,1952 November 26, December 2-3, 5, 8-9 (Box 174)
            - Dale Pollack,1952 December 18, 1953 January 9, 14 (Box 174)
            - W. R. G. Baker,1953 January 14 (Box 174)
            - Jesse E. Brown,1953 January 28 (Box 174)
            - Continued--Kenneth A. Chittick,1953 February 23 (Box 174)
            - Paul R. Bennett,1953 February 13 (Box 174)
            - David Sarnoff,1953 February 20, 24-25, 27 (Box 174)
            - Robert B. Dome,1953 March 13 (Box 175)
            - Conway P. Coe,1953 March 24 (Box 175)
            - Bernard Dunlevy Loughlin,1953 April 23, 30, May 28 (Box 175)
            - Charles B. Jolliffe,1953 April 28 (Box 175)
            - Isidor Goldberg,1953 April 30 (Box 175)
            - Elmer W. Engstrom,1953 June 17 (Box 175)
            - Stuart W. Seeley,1953 June 18 (Box 175)
            - Edwin A. Armstrong,1953 August 28, September 1 (Box 175)
            - John H Bose,1953 May 6 (Box 175)
            - Alfred N. Goldsmith,1953 May 13 (Box 175)
            - Edwin H. Armstrong,1953 September 2, 10, 17, 23, October 6, 15-16, 22-23, 29-30, November 4-5, 20, 24, December 3, 18, 23, 30 (Box 176)
            - C. R. Runyon Jr.,1954 January 7 (Box 176)
            - Charles M. Srebroff,1954 January 14-15, 26 (Box 176)
            - James Robert Day,1954 January 14 (Box 176)
            - Arthur Freed,1954 January 28 (Box 177)
            - Paul A. de Mars and Joseph D. Black,1952 June 25 (Box 177)
            - Harold O. Peterson and Harry Tunick,1952 August 12 (Box 177)
            - Benjamin E. Shackelford,1952 August 15, 18 (Box 177)
            - Elmer E. Lucher,1952 August 29 (Box 177)
            - Robert E. Schock and George W. Pettengill,1952 September 4 (Box 177)
            - Ewen C. Anderson,1952 September 10 (Box 177)
            - Ernest V. Amy,1952 September 17 (Box 177)
          - Oral Argument,1952 September 19 (Box 177)
          - Depositions
            - Clarence W. Hansell,1952 October 3 (Box 177)
          - Oral Argument,1952 October 23 (Box 177)
          - Depositions
            - Harry G. Grover,1952 October 24 (Box 177)
            - Stuart W. Seeley,1950 September 28, 29, 1952 October 28, 1953 June 18 (Box 177)
            - Orrin E. Dunlap Junior, Phil L. Rodier and James G. Norton,1952 November 3 (Box 177)
            - James G. Norton,1952 November 13 (Box 177)
          - Oral Argument,1952 November 20 (Box 177)
          - Depositions
            - Dale Pollack,1952 December 18, 1953 January 9 (Box 177)
            - Jesse E. Brown,1953 January 28 (Box 177)
            - Kenneth A. Chittick and Paul R. Bennett,1953 February 13 (Box 177)
            - Bernard Dunlevy Loughlin,1953 May 28 (Box 178)
            - Elmer W. Engstrom,1953 June 17 (Box 178)
            - Continued Deposition--Stuart W. Seeley--1953 June 18 (Box 178)
            - David G. C. Luck,1953 June 26 (Box 178)
          - Examination--Edwin H. Armstrong,1949 November 10, 14-15, 17-18, 21-23, 28, 30, December 2, 12 (Box 178)
          - Depositions
            - Edwin H. Armstrong,1949 December 13-14, 16, 19, 1950 January 13, 16-18, 23, February 3, 6, 10, 20 (Box 178)
          - Edwin H Armstrong (Box 179)
            - Examination by Fowler,1949 February 14-15, March 2-4 (Box 179)
            - Examination by Zeller,1953 October 23, 29, 30, November 5, 12 (Scrap Paper with Handwritten Calculations Inserted) 20, (Cover Page Annotated) 24, 30, December 3, 9, 23, 30 (Box 179)
          - Depositions
            - Harry Tunick,1951 October 4, 16, 23 (Box 179)
            - Edwin H. Armstrong,1953 November 5, 12, 17, 20, 24, 30 (Box 180)
          - Oral Arguments,1951 October 22, 1952 September 19, October 10, 23, November 20, 1954 January 20, February 3 (Box 180)
          - Depositions
            - Murray G. Crosby,1951 April 6, 10, 12, 1951 May 3, 10 (Box 180)
            - Lewis M. Clement,1952 March 6 (Box 180)
          - Stenographer's Minutes,1948 November 1, 1949 March 11, May 3 (Box 180)
          - Examination--Winfield R. Koch,1952 April 24 (Box 180)
          - Depositions
            - George E. Folk,1930 April 8 (Box 180)
            - David Hulfish,1930 April 8 (Box 180)
          - Technical Conference--Dr. Bowles, undated (Box 180)
          - Digest of Testimony--Digest of Deposition of Plaintiff Edwin H. Armstrong, 1949 (Box 181)
          - Digest of Plaintiff's Testimony--Topical Abstract of Deposition of Plaintiff Armstrong--Digest of Deposition of Plaintiff Edwin H. Armstrong--Analysis of Mr. Hoxie's Examination of Plaintiff Edwin H. Armstrong, 1949, undated (Box 181)
          - Digests of Defendants' Testimony--Testimonies of Kenneth A. Chittick--Orville Dow--Clarence W. Hansell--O.B. Hanson, Nils E. Lindenblad--Harold O. Peterson--George M. Nixon--Ralph W. George--Gano Dunn--Walter Spiegel--Leo J. Galanek--Joe W. Morrison--Elmer W. Engstrom--Stuart W. Seeley--Edward W. Wilby--Dominic Schmit--Murray G. Crosby--Chester M. Sinnett--Arthur Van Dyck--Harry Tunick--David G Luck, 1950-1951 (Box 181)
          - Digest of Deposition of Marcus. W. Glaser,1951 April 27 (Box 181, Folder 1)
          - Digest of Harry Tunick Examination, 1950 (Box 181, Folder 2)
          - Summaries of Important Facts in Depositions of Witnesses, undated (Box 181, Folder 3)
      - Patent Related Documents
        - PD 1-520--General, (15 Folders) (Box 182, Folder 1-15)
        - PD 521-684--General, (2 Folders) (Box 183, Folder 1-2)
        - PD 685-744--Hansell Docket 8821 (Box 183, Folder 3)
        - PD 785-777--The RCA Offers (Box 183, Folder 4)
        - PD 778-837--Hathaway Documents (Box 183, Folder 5)
        - PD 1002-1018--Hansell Notes 1934-1935 (Box 183, Folder 6)
        - PD 1019-1181--Crosby "FM Noise Characteristics" Papers (Box 183, Folder 7)
        - PD 1182-1199--Crosby Docket 5235 (Box 183, Folder 8)
        - PD 1200-1249--Lindenblad Docket 4366 (Box 183, Folder 9)
        - PD 1250-1294--Lindenblad Docket 4683 (Box 183, Folder 10)
        - PD 1295-1347--Crosby Docket 5167 (Box 183, Folder 11)
        - PD 1348-1452--George Docket 6787 (Box 183, Folder 12)
        - PD 1453-1477--Conklin Docket 4213 (Box 183, Folder 13)
        - PD 1478-1485--Salzberg Docket 4871 (Box 183, Folder 14)
        - PD 1486-1489--Usselman Docket 2318 (Box 183, Folder 15)
        - PD 1490-1538--George Notebooks 2, 3 and 4 (Box 183, Folder 16)
        - PD 1700-1730A--Dow Notebook Number 4 (Box 183, Folder 17)
        - PD 1731-1743--Dow Notebook Number 5 (Box 183, Folder 18)
        - PD 1744-1774--Schock Notebook Number 2 (Box 183, Folder 19)
        - PD 1794-1803--F-18-4 Circuit Diagrams (Box 184, Folder 1)
        - PD 1804-1818--License Bulletin 761 (Box 184, Folder 2)
        - PD 1819-1820--Luck Notebook Number 1850 (Box 184, Folder 3)
        - PD 1830-1834--Hansell RCA Docket 18,112 (Box 184, Folder 4)
        - PD 1835-1842--RCA Reports LR-1833 and 1850 to Regal Electronics Corporation (Box 184, Folder 5)
        - PD 1843-1848--Purington Letters to Beverage and Roberts (Box 184, Folder 6)
        - PD 1956-1986--Schock Notebook Number 1 (Box 184, Folder 7)
        - PD 1987-2003--Schock Notebook Number 2 (Box 184, Folder 8)
        - PD 2004-2025--Documents Requested in Memo of 1951 June 18 (Box 184, Folder 9)
        - PD 2026-2043--Documents Requested in Memo of 1951 June 18 (Box 184, Folder 10)
        - PD 2044-2063--Documents Requested in Memo of 1951 June 18 (Box 184, Folder 11)
        - PD 2064-2101--Documents Requested in Memo of 1951 June 18 (Box 184, Folder 12)
        - PD 2102-2110--Crosby RCA Docket Number 10287 (Box 184, Folder 13)
        - PD 2131-2136--General (Box 184, Folder 14)
        - PD 2137-2141--V.D. Landon Notes and Diagrams for 1935 on work done regarding Camden FM Receiver (Box 184, Folder 15)
        - PD 2142-2144--Hathaway Exhibits 4, 5 and 6 (Box 184, Folder 16)
        - PD 2145-2183--1939 Buzalski Empire State Records (Box 184, Folder 17)
        - PD 2184-2212--Schock Notebook Number 2, pages 66-89, Crosby Exhibit 80 (Box 184, Folder 18)
        - PD 2214-2259--Hathaway Documents (Box 184, Folder 19)
        - PD 2260-2263--Regarding Publication of F-18-9 Report of Crosby (Box 184, Folder 20)
        - PD 2266-2267--Hathaway Docket Number 18735 (Box 184, Folder 21)
        - PD 2268-2274--Morris Docket Number 20214 (Box 184, Folder 22)
        - PD 2275-2299--The RCA Offer (Box 184, Folder 23)
        - PD 2302-2327--1924 Belfast Work (Box 184, Folder 24)
        - PD 2328-2417--Documents relating to 1927, 1928, 1929 and 1930 research program on 5 meters (Box 184, Folder 25)
        - PD 2418-2464--Belfast Work, Poldhu tests and blueprints (Box 184, Folder 26)
        - PD 2465-2467--Schairer 1939 correspondence (Box 184, Folder 27)
        - PD 2468A-2595--AT and T documents (Box 184, Folder 28)
        - PD 2596-2619--RCA Licensee letters relating to Notice of Infringement (Box 184, Folder 29)
        - PD 2620-2626--Beverage Notebook Number 9 and Peterson Notebook Number 1 regarding Belfast transmitter (Box 184, Folder 30)
        - PD 2661-2664--Minutes of RCA Planning Committee 12/7/43 (Box 184, Folder 31)
        - PD 2665-2769--RCA Planning Committee Report on FM (Box 184, Folder 32)
        - PD 2770-2804--Belfast Operations (Box 184, Folder 33)
        - PD 2805-2836--Hansell to Cunningham 1951 November 5 (Box 184, Folder 34)
        - PD 2837-2841--General (Box 184, Folder 35)
        - PD 2842-2851--Schairer to Sarnoff 1939 November 10 (Box 184, Folder 36)
        - PD 2852-3135--General, (6 Folders) (Box 185, Folder 1-6)
      - Uncatalogued Documents--Photostats
        - Reports, Correspondence, Memoranda and Diagrams, 1930-1951, (8 Folders) (Box 185, Folder 7-14)
          - Includes Blueprints, 1901-1953 (Box 185, Folder 15)
        - Reports, Correspondence, Memoranda and Diagrams, 1924-1952, (11 Folders) (Box 186, Folder 1-11)
        - Excerpts from Notebooks of Murray G. Crosby, Notebooks 1-1b and 5-6, 1929-1930 (Box 186, Folder 12)
        - Excerpts from Notebooks of Murray G. Crosby, Notebooks 7-9, 1931 (Box 186, Folder 13)
        - Excerpts from Notebooks of Murray G. Crosby, Notebooks 10-13 and KKZ Frequency and Phase Modulation Tests, 1934-1942 (Box 186, Folder 14)
        - Reports, Correspondence, Memoranda and Diagrams, 1929-1953, (14 Folders) (Box 187, Folder 1-14)
        - Reports, Correspondence, Memoranda and Diagrams, 1929-1952, (12 Folders) (Box 188, Folder 1-12)
        - Reports, Correspondence, Memoranda and Diagrams, 1926-1949, (14 Folders) (Box 189, Folder 1-14)
        - Reports, Correspondence, Memoranda and Diagrams, 1923-1952, (13 Folders) (Box 190, Folder 1-13)
        - Reports, Correspondence, Memoranda and Diagrams, 1927-1946, (5 Folders) (Box 191, Folder 1-5)
      - Abstracts
        - Volume--1929-1940 (Box 191)
        - Volume--1941-1949 (Box 191)
        - 1930-1948, undated, (2 Folders) (Box 191, Folder 6-7)
        - Abstracts and Other Data on Case, 1939-1953, undated, (3 Folders) (Box 191, Folder 8-10)
        - Abstract Class--1 through 9, 1931-1949, (4 Folders) (Box 254, Folder 1-4)
        - Abstract Chronological
          - Nos. 1 and 2, 1931-1939, (2 Folders) (Box 254, Folder 5-6)